const QUIZ = [
{
number: 1,
question: 'What is necessary for a scene to be termed "Improvisation"?',
ans1: 'It has to be funny.',
ans2: 'It needs at least two people.',
ans3: 'Everything must be made up on the spot.',
ans4: 'People need to be watching it.',
correctAnswer: 'Everything must be made up on the spot.'
},
{
number: 2,
question: 'What is a "Back Line" in Improv?',
ans1: 'A game where all of the imrprovsers  on stage do a Conga Line backwards',
ans2: 'A term for when someone says a line with their back to the audience',
ans3: 'A game where everyone must say their sentences backwards',
ans3: 'When all improvisers not in a scene line up along the back of the stage',
correctAnswer: 'When all improvisers not in a scene line up along the back of the stage'
},
{
number: 3,
question: 'Which of these famous comedians did NOT graduate from the Second City Training Program?',
ans1: 'Steve Carell',
ans2: 'Tina Fey',
ans3: 'Bill Murray',
ans4: 'Amy Schumer',
correctAnswer: 'Amy Schumer'
},
{
number: 4,
question: 'What three things are essential to the start of a good improv scene?',
ans1: 'Who, What, Where',
ans2: 'Characters, Accents, Object work',
ans3: 'One Improviser, A Suggestion From the Audience, A Stage',
ans4: 'Two Improvisers, A Chair on Stage, A Back Line',
correctAnswer: 'Who, What, Where'
},
{
number: 5,
question: 'Which of the following terms is a method for editing a scene?',
ans1: '"Tossing the Scene"',
ans2: '"Sweeping"',
ans3: '"Making New"',
ans4: '"Creationism"',
correctAnswer: '"Sweeping"'
},
{
number: 6,
question:'Which of the following terms is NOT an editing method?',
ans1: 'Tag Out',
ans2: 'Focus Edit',
ans3: 'Twist In',
ans4: 'Revolving Door',
correctAnswer: 'Twist In'
},
{
number: 7,
question:'What is the main strategy for being a good improviser?',
ans1: 'Saying "Yes, and..."',
ans2: 'Being funny',
ans3: 'Looking good',
ans4: 'Having a few drinks before performing',
correctAnswer: 'Saying "Yes, and..."'
},
{
number: 8,
question:'What are the basic rules for the classic game of "Freeze"?',
ans1: 'Everyone on stage must perform a scene without moving.',
ans2: 'New improvisers must take the physical position of the people in the current scene and start a new scene.',
ans3: 'Improvisers must do a scene where they only talk about frozen foods.',
ans4: 'The scene must take place in a really cold setting.',
correctAnswer: 'New improvisers must take the physical position of the people in the current scene and start a new scene.'
},
{
number: 9,
question:'If a scene is not going anywhere, what can you do to save it?',
ans1: 'Panic and run off stage',
ans2: 'Kill off your character',
ans3: 'Heighten your emotional response',
ans4: 'Nothing, it cannot be saved',
correctAnswer: 'Heighten your emotional response'
},
{
number: 10,
question:'On stage, what is the cue that a scene or game is over?',
ans1: 'The lights go off or the host calls "Scene!"',
ans2:'All performers look to the audience and say "We\'re done!"',
ans3: 'The performers walk off stage.',
ans4: 'A character dies.',
correctAnswer: 'The lights go off or the host calls "Scene!"'
}
]




